Good day, Bashar.
>> And of you. Good day.
>> Crop formations.
>> Crop formations. Yes.
>> Yes. Uh for about 15 years, I've been
researching uh both.
>> Oh, that sounds like fun.
>> Yes, it is. Um physical research as well
as spiritual research.
>> Yes. Yes.
>> The two go hand in hand because there is
nothing non-spiritual about physical
reality.
>> That's right.
>> That was a big lesson for some. it
[laughter]
the energy um I have consciously chosen
to
>> to study um
along that path and pretty much as soon
as I got into it and somebody here
earlier mentioned the Arcturians.
>> Yes. [snorts]
Uh what I believe is well through
synchronicities um arcturians have
played a role and have uh all the beings
in the inagram have played a role as
well as other spirit beings, other
guides, other levels of dimensional
consciousness and even the consciousness
of your own world individually and
collectively have played a part in the
creation of that language of that
multi-dimensional imagery that aids and
assists you in being reflective. of who
you really are or at least giving you a
hint and a clue of the path to follow to
discover yourselves.
>> Yes. And that was actually my next
question was
>> well thank you for allowing us to answer
it.
>> Thank you
my involvement uh in the studying and
maybe dissemination of that information.
Um
Arcturians uh a particular role they
play. Why is it the synchronicities are
coming from?
>> It's a stabilizing energy, an aligning
energy
>> that allows one more ease of alignment
with the true core frequencies of their
being.
>> That's what the Arcturus energy plays a
part in doing.
>> And I heard you mention earlier they're
not physical. They are
>> not as you understand physicality. No.
>> Okay. More of a consciousness.
>> Yes.
>> Okay.
That's question number one.
>> All right. was basically
reminding me consciously of what I think
I already know unconsciously.
>> Thank you.
>> So I'll continue to do that work because
that uh brings me my highest excitement.
>> Yes.
>> Second and last um I was recently in
Mount Shasta.
>> All right.
>> While I was there, there was a group of
about 150 um people from South America
who were there for what we would call a
contact.
>> Yes. And um I believe I saw um Craft.
>> Oh, all right.
>> That was um associated with that
contact.
>> All right.
>> There was a specific name that I was
unaware of and was wondering if you knew
uh anything about this particular um
>> are you referring?
>> It's actually Antourell or Antel.
I am unaware of this name yet. Um,
a researcher friend of mine, Paula
Harris, was there, witnessed it, has
written a story since, and the name
hasn't rang a bell. I don't know what
consciousness this is, what energy it
is, and very curious because I've never
heard. It
>> is an offshoot extension of the hybrid
civilization that will be one of the
first to have open contact with your
civilization.
>> Okay.
>> Does that help you?
>> That absolutely helps me. All right.
>> Thank you. That's all that I have for
you.
>> All right. Thank you then. That's all I
have for you.
>> There you go. Thank you. [applause]
>> Good day, Bashar.
>> And you good day.
>> First of all, let me thank you for your
all your teachings and uh I just want to
tell you that I appreciate you so much.
>> All right. Well, we thank you for the
co-creation.
Um
um my uh highest excitement uh seems to
be lately uh
um regarding psychedelics.
>> All right.
>> Plant plant teacher teachers.
>> Yes.
>> And I am curious about the uh big
picture on ayaska and DMT and and the
difference uh thereof. Well, they are
guides and specific frequencies to allow
you to experience altered states that
give you an understanding of what kind
of vibrational states you can come from
in life. What kind of vibrational states
you can recreate within yourself without
necessarily requiring the teacher of the
plant all the time. They are
opportunities to be able to hone your
senses, to be more able to perceive
things that were here to for invisible
that are all around you all the time. to
allow your senses to peer into other
dimensions and begin to break down the
veils and the barriers between what you
consider to be physical reality and
other levels of dimensional reality.
That's what they're there to do, to
remind you of your connection to source,
your connection to spirit, to allow you
to function more holistically as a human
being, as a part of nature and
expression of nature on the earth, and
to allow you to perceive that you are
connected to much more than you may
think. But once they teach you this, the
idea is also that you don't really need
them any longer and that you can
recreate those states within yourself
anytime you so desire.
>> Awesome.
>> Yes.
>> Um [laughter]
>> Oh, well put any
>> way to sum up. any any danger any danger
I should be aware of while using
>> the only idea you might consider to be
dangerous which isn't really is that you
have to be prepared to face whatever it
is they are going to show you about
yourself and any fears you may be
harboring but it's not really dangerous
it might just feel like a wild ride
>> well one of my fears is that I may be
given false information and uh
>> by the plant
>> yes You can't be given false information
by the plant. What you can do, however,
is that if you're holding on to certain
belief systems that cause the
information to be filtered in a way
that's misaligned with what really would
resonate with you, then you can
certainly have that experience. But
always look to yourself to see that
you're the one that's going to be
coloring that information. The
information from the plant cannot be
false.
>> Great.
>> Does that help? Yes.
>> Always bring it back to yourself. Always
take responsibility for what it is you
are perceiving. It doesn't matter if
someone else actually even has an
intention to deceive you or falsify
anything. Always take responsibility for
your part in the co-creation and you
will always be able to unairringly guide
yourself back to a center point no
matter what kind of information you are
being fed. Yes.
>> Yes.
>> You can see through any illusion. The
more transparent to yourself you become,
you can see through any illusion. The
more transparent to yourself you become.
This is why the greatest sages, the
greatest masters, and the greatest
teachers, and the greatest literature on
your planet has for centuries boiled
down the ultimate answer, the ultimate
idea to a simple two words, know
thyself.
>> Yes. And then you will understand any
reflections you may encounter because
you will understand it is all
reflections. And if something is out of
alignment,
look to yourself first.
>> Yes.
>> Yes. And that that [clears throat] is my
intention too.
>> All right. Then if it is your intention,
allow it to flow out through your actual
actions.
Remember true knowing is synonymous with
behavior. The things you know are true,
you just do. If I ask you to walk across
a room, you don't sit there and go,
"Well, I think I can." Well, wait, I
believe I can walk across the room. No,
you just walk. The things you know are
true. You just do. Action and knowing
are synonymous.
So, if your behavior doesn't exhibit it,
that means you don't quite know it yet.
So, keep digging.
>> Yes.
So part of my interest with uh these uh
plant medicines is that I I wish to help
my
>> sister to come out of the downward
spiral that she's been in for 25 years.
>> All right. But again, you heard us talk
to someone else about doing your best to
be an example of what she may choose,
but you have to allow her to choose her
path, even if it's negative. She may not
be ready to take you up on a different
course of action.
>> If she is, she will. But the only way
she will is if you simply provide the
opportunity by being the best example
you can be of someone who if they choose
that path reflects the joy that she may
in her heart wish to have but again may
be too afraid to jump on, maybe too
afraid to act on. So, if you can allow
yourself to impart information that you
have learned from the plants in a way
that will allow her to not be afraid to
get in touch with her own deep-seated
fear-based beliefs and allow her to let
them go, then she may walk that path
side by side. But if she chooses not to,
there is not much you can do to change
her mind. Do remember however
there is never any reason in any way,
shape or form to despair. You are all
eternal, infinite, indestructible
beings. If it doesn't happen now, it'll
happen sometime
because you have all of infinity to
explore who you are. And by your own
definition, infinity never ends.
>> Yes,
>> that's very reassuring.
>> Well, that's just the way things are.
[laughter]
>> Does that help you?
>> Yes, it does very much. Thank you so
much.
>> You are so very much welcome.
>> Uh, one more thing. Um, what is this
about uh triple numbers and uh
meaningful numbers like 911 or 322?
Many people will use the idea of numeric
to create signs and symbols and road
markers so that when they experience the
synchronicity of those numbers coming
up, it will be like a sign that you are
in the correct vibration and in align
with your path.
>> Even like 911 is usually has negative
connotations.
>> Well, you've given it one, but you can
also recognize it has a positive one.
Think of the idea of the phoenix rising
from the ashes. Yes.
>> I did not know that was related to 9/11.
>> I am saying it is related to the
incident that you are relating 9/11 to.
>> Oh, okay.
>> So, the idea is you can recognize again
as we said earlier that something can be
generated from a fear-based belief.
Something can be created, a situation
can absolutely be manifested from a
negative point of view. That doesn't
mean that you have to use those symbols
in a negative way yourself just because
other people may relate to it that way.
>> Mhm.
>> Yes.
>> All right. So, give yourself an
opportunity to recognize 11 is a power
number, a gateway to higher dimensions
of higher consciousness. And nine is the
number of the completion of a cycle. So
if you're completing an old cycle that
that activity that that incident
represents, then you can take that as
the beginning of a new cycle that begins
with 11, which means you're going up a
level. You're going up a dimension.
You're going up a notch and you're going
up in vibration. So that if you change
the way you go about doing things and
relating to other people on your planet,
then such things will never have to
happen again in the negative context
that they happened before.
>> Wow. I have arrived to this venue this
morning at exactly 911.
>> All right. Well, you see there's
positive benefit in that.
>> I I even had to go around the the the
block once because I missed the
entrance.
>> You missed nothing. [laughter]
>> No, I mean when I came the second time,
it was exactly 911.
>> So the idea of those numerical symbols
can in their most fundamental sense
simply represent perfect timing. Yes.
>> Yes. All right. Does this help?
>> Thank you very much. Helps a lot.
[laughter]
[applause]
>> Hi Vishar.
>> How are you? Good day.
>> Good day to you Andy Esani. I've been
looking forward to speaking with you in
this moment.
>> All right. And through what story will
you be doing so?
>> Well, it's going to start with a
father's day story.
>> Father's Day story. Father. Yes, cuz it
is Father's Day honor.
>> Yes, we understand.
>> I was wondering, do you guys have those
days? No, you don't. Every day.
>> Every day is a celebration.
>> Yes.
>> Okay. Um,
>> we do not delineate the idea of special
days in that way specifically.
>> In what way do you?
>> We don't.
>> You just don't. There are recognitions
of certain things that happened in what
you would call our history that are
noted for their particular vibrational
resonance, but we don't surround them
with the kinds of rituals that you do.
We simply experience that vibration and
move forward.
>> Okay.
Well, I just wanted to express that
since we're talking about stories, I
want to share with you how my dad would
say that. He'd say,
>> "All right,
>> I tell you a story." Cuz he likes pirate
stuff. So he would say that. So I just
wanted to share that with you. And my
story actually starts a bit with my dad.
>> Yes.
>> We were we just saw the movie Thor.
>> Oh.
>> And it it was I didn't really want to
see it at first, but he's like, "No, you
really will love seeing this movie. You
got to see it."
>> And did you?
>> I did. And I was exhilarated. And then
you know if you guys because I saw these
different beings in the in the galaxy
other races and
>> I felt such a connection to them and I
wish I was there with them actually the
different
>> Does that mean you're also going to go
see the latest movie entertainment that
also deals with other beings in the
galaxy?
>> Um there's one that I do plan to go see.
It's the
>> Is it the color green
>> green lantern? Yes. And I did have a
question about that. There there's been
talk that
>> um you know due um as open contact
becomes well more open that um society
will start
>> [snorts]
>> um showing more of what other races look
like. Is that right? What they not right
but
>> do you mean will your depictions in your
science fiction stories become more
accurately representative of some of the
races that exist? Yes.
>> Yes.
>> Okay. And does that movie reflect that?
>> Some.
>> Some. Okay.
>> Now again, remember anything you can
imagine is real because you cannot
imagine non-existence. But when I say
some, I mean some that are relevant to
anything that you could experience as
being somewhat similar to your
understanding of reality. All of them
are real in their own context, but may
not be relevant to your dimension of
experience. But some actually are.
>> Okay. Thank you.
So when I was watching the movie Thor, I
was I felt like I wanted to be there and
I was kind of meditating on that later
on after the movie and my inner my inner
guidance told me because I was asking
well why am I not there if I like it so
much? You are you are not but you are
>> right and and I received that well that
is part of you that is you
>> that's why you resonate
>> to it
>> right and you're on earth to bring that
here
>> yes
>> as an emanation.
>> Yes you're the conduit. or the valve
through which you can bring that energy
down to earth
>> and give off a vibration that will allow
choices to be made that are in alignment
with that frequency.
>> Yes, I was very happy.
>> That's why you have these kinds of
stories.
That's why one of the most powerful
storytelling tools you have is movies
because it really gives you an
interactive experience
and what you call theme parks. It gives
you an interactive experience of story
and thus it sinks in because you are
actually viscerally there in the
vibration and together unified in many
ways.
I feel that a lot.
>> And yes,
>> the next
>> we wish to also point out a very
interesting polarity happening at this
time with respect to these kinds of
stories that involve what you call
extraterrestrial beings because uh in
this moment right now you actually have
presented at the same time a completely
polarized idea of this notion in your
entertainment.
You have the idea we have just discussed
of a story that involves the idea of
what you would call an interstellar
peacekeeping core of extraterrestrials.
And at the same time, you're also
premiering
>> the Transformers movie.
>> That and also another one called Falling
Skies where your world is dominated by
extraterrestrials on your television
sets.
So you have presented the polarity for
yourself so that you can explore and
play with the idea of both sides
simultaneously. You're bringing these
creations closer and closer and closer
to the center point so that you can
really experience the balance of the
dark and the light, the balance of the
negative and the positive and really
decide what you prefer by exploring
these stories so close to each other on
top of each other even.
Good timing.
>> Yeah. Thank you for expanding on that.
Um, I remember the first time I heard
you speak of the EIL, the Shaol
Shaloniah.
>> Yes.
>> And all the senses in my being just
perked up.
>> Oh, right.
>> And I I got goosebumps.
>> They are part of your story. You are
part of their
>> They are. They are. And I have
>> They are one of the other hybrid races.
the first one that will contact your
world for those asking the question in
their minds, what's the shaalonia?
>> And I I got goosebumps and I I never get
goosebumps I that I remember except for
when I'm cold. And I so I thought I
always heard people talk about getting
goosebumps but I've never got them. And
then so when I got them I was like
>> well I can't say that anymore.
>> I know, right? I can't say that anymore.
And and I was like wow that is true. And
and as I listened to it the the the
gooseups just they were like waves. They
they just continue to like electrify me.
>> Yes. And
>> do you understand fundamentally what
that effect is? You call goosebumps?
>> I don't. No.
>> The idea is that
they will be constrictions around the
hair follicles that will allow the hair
follicles to rise up and become more
receptive antennas to that energy.
>> Wow, that's neat.
>> Yes.
>> Thank you for expanding on that.
[sighs and gasps]
And so as as I continued to listen to to
that, I I I just closed my eyes and I
got a sense as if I was there with them.
Even even now, like I feel like I can
>> tap into that. [clears throat] And um
there's been certain occurrences and
instances. Um one has been all of the
month of May. Um, I saw these clouds
over Mount Baldi, that's close to where
I live, that I've never seen like that
ever before. They look like the ones on
Mount Shasta, you know, and they were
over Mount Baldi, the range. And and I
the whole month of May, I haven't seen
them June, but I just thought, wow, that
is so amazing. I felt like that was
their presence showing themselves. Well,
in a sense, it is more the idea of your
collective consciousness creating
symbolic representations of what you are
becoming more and more aware of and in a
sense preparing yourselves for something
more solid. You're using your own
weather. You're using your own clouds to
create shapes to represent what you will
actually ultimately see in physical
form.
>> Okay?
>> You're preparing yourselves
>> for contact with those forms. They're
like placeholders.
>> [snorts]
>> And um
>> because you are changing your weather,
>> right? Um, I was wondering if you could
tell a bit of a story of maybe some of
the things you know that the Shaoliniah
or the AI would like for us to know at
this time where we're at on earth and
how we can um be more open to them
>> and how
>> water is very important.
The more you allow yourself
to allow crystallization,
purification,
higher resonance energies
to in that sense interact with the
structure of the water that you drink.
the more you will aid and assist in the
clarification of your bodily systems, in
the increasing of the silicon in your
systems to make you more receptive to
our frequencies, more receptive to our
communications, so that you may receive
those communications and the beginning
of dialogues that will lay down the
foundations and lay down the paths of
our eventual contact. Water is key.
>> Thank you.
>> That is the message from them. I I heard
them. Thank you. Um
I was wondering if you could share some
knowledge I've the different
visuals of some of the or uh extr
extraterrestrial races such as the
palladians, the Arcturans, the Syrians
and the Argians.
Do they look similar? Plleadenss in that
sense are genetically connected to you.
You are like longlost cousins. So in
that sense they are very human form.
The idea of uh the physical race in the
star system of Sirius is that which has
been described as somewhat amphibious uh
in that sense somewhat salamanderish.
The idea of the non-physical
consciousness connected to Sirius is of
course non-physical. The idea of
arcturous energy in that sense is also a
non-physical consciousness that does not
have form in the way you would
understand it but is represented by the
idea of the glowing orange orbs that
many of you have seen.
>> Oh okay.
>> What you are referring to as a Gan in
that sense is actually known by another
frequency altogether that is very
ancient and they do not share the idea
of physical form as you know it.
There are other races that you will
encounter eventually in time that are
not like your species at all. We have
from time to time described some of
these. We will not really go into the
list right now, but will at what you
call a future time focus on the idea of
a transmission that describes many of
these races.
>> Okay. Thank you.
>> Thank you for the sharing of your story.
>> Thank you. I have some more if that's
okay.
>> Um
Your story has an epilogue.
>> Yes. Yes. Um,
>> make it brief.
>> Okay. Um, I have heard you speak of the
span between 2010 and 2015 and the
sensing of energy at that moment.
>> Yes. And the splitting prism.
>> And can you speak a more on the
splitting prism and where the energy on
earth is at this sensing of the energy?
>> The trains are already leaving the
station. The tracks are getting slightly
farther and farther apart. Be on the
train you wish to be on before you can
never reach the other track.
>> Right?
>> That's all we will say for now.
>> Okay.
>> Take everything we have said in the
transmission over the course of what you
call these three days and apply it to
decide and choose what story you will
be, what track you will be on.
>> Thank you. I am
>> all right. Thank you.
Let us say good day to you this day of
your time. How are you all?
[applause]
>> All right. All right. Thank you. Thank
you once again for the co-creation of
these interactions and the allowance of
this transmission in this way. At this
time, we would like to begin this
transmission by reminding you that it is
titled Nature's Social Network.
The idea being that there are a variety
of ways that different elements,
different expressions in nature
communicate with one another because you
are all immersed in a web of energy and
information.
But there are very specific ways in
which these connections in the energy
web are expressed depending upon the
expression of nature.
First we remind you that you do not
exist in nature. You are nature. Your
bodies are an expression of the nature
of the reality that you have chosen to
experience.
We know that for some time many
individuals within humanity
have in the past thought of themselves
as being separate from nature. Maybe
living in it, maybe being surrounded by
it, but not necessarily considering
themselves to be of it. But you are.
Your world has given you the ability to
crystallize a physical form out of the
elements of nature that exist in your
reality at your vibratory level of
energy rendering that energy
crystallizing that energy into what you
call the perception of matter. So you
are absolutely an extension of nature on
earth.
But in societies that exist on your
planet who have forgotten that, not
everyone but many, then there is an
important need to allow yourselves to
begin to experience yourselves once
again as you did long ago
as expressions of nature. This would be
the first step in being capable of
perceiving and connecting in a conscious
way to the web of information, the web
of energy that connects you all that
connects all nature, all things in your
experience of reality.
But we will begin by describing one of
the ways or two of the ways or maybe
three of the ways we will see that
different expressions in nature have of
expressing this connectivity and
utilizing
this connectivity in a variety of ways
to support life
to support consciousness and its
expressions in your reality. Let us
begin with the trees. We have talked
about the idea from time to time that
trees in a sense are very much like
antenna protruding upwards into the sky
from the earth and the way they are
structured based on certain mathematical
ratios. They are sensitive to many
different kinds of higher level energies
and they can like an antenna receive
those energies in the very fine tips of
their branches and leaves and transform
and transmit and step down and allow
that energy to be guided into the earth
to be used in a variety of ways to be
tapped into by whatever needs to tap
into that energy at whatever frequency
is relevant.
for the different life form that may
choose to tap into that energy and
utilize that connective energy web. But
more than that, deep underground in the
roots of trees and plants, there is
another expression of this connective
network, this social network. In any
given group of trees, you will find in
these forests that the roots of the
trees in whatever way they may choose to
spread out are also connected to what
has been termed in your language the
mycelial network. The mcelial network is
a type of growth of fungal filaments
that attach to the roots and go from one
tree to another to another to another to
another throughout the grove throughout
the forest. So in a forest where the
trees are dense all the trees are
connected underground by their roots
through this fungal mycelial network.
Now this network of filaments that
connect all these roots
are not only for the purpose of
transmitting energy are not only for the
purpose of transmitting information but
they provide a true demonstration of the
intelligence inherent in all life forms
on your planet whether you think they
are necessarily intelligent or not.
Not only can information and energy be
transmitted through the mycelial network
in much the same way that your neural
net in your brains transmit impulses,
electrical impulses between all the
different neurons. This mycelial network
can transmit those kinds of impulses but
also serves many other functions.
The mcelial network can actually
transmit water from one tree to another
where water may be lacking. So the trees
that are receiving more water will know
through the information of the mcelial
network which trees may not be receiving
enough water and they will actually
intentionally send more water through
the mycelial network to the trees that
require it. They will send food and
nutrients through the mcelial network as
well to the trees that require it. This
is a true transport system underground
for the trees of a forest. And there is
vast amount of information, vast amount
of exchange going on under your feet
when you walk through a forest. Like an
underground subway network that you may
not even have been aware of going on
just a few feet underground, right under
your feet. All this talk, all this
communication, food stuffs, water,
impulses back and forth. It's very busy
going on under there. It's its own kind
of city.
Now, sometimes you can tell where these
mycelial networks might be because one
of the offshoots of the fungal filaments
might be that at a certain point
mushrooms and other fungal forms will
come up through the ground, showing you
exactly where some of these mycelial
networks may have blossomed into another
expression and form of life that then
aids and assists and adds to the overall
communication web going on in that
forest.
One of the things that has come down
through stories and legends on your
planet is the [clears throat] idea of
what you call fairy rings, which are
usually described as the idea of
mushrooms in a circle forming a fairy
ring as you call it to which different
forms of nature spirits and elementals
may be attracted or you may be able if
you are able to perceive them find them
gathering in those areas. This is
because it is their form of connecting
to the mycelial network. They actually
can use that ring and it grows in a ring
for the purpose of actually allowing
other beings of different frequencies to
tap into that network when they need to.
In a sense, you could say
euphemistically, the fairy rings of
different kinds of mushrooms that crop
up from the mcelial network underground
so that there can be an interface with
different kinds of nature spirits to
that web of information are almost in a
sense kind of like their Stonehenge. You
understand? So it forms that circle to
capture that energy to transmit that
energy in a very efficient way. It forms
a kind of energy web lens by being in a
circular form and that helps aid and
assist in the amplification of the
energy of the information and it also
transmits it to the particular vibration
needed for the elementals and the nature
spirits to be able to access that
information based on their nature.
Now, there are other forms of
communication and social networks in
nature.
When you're talking about the idea of
the elements themselves, not elementals,
but the elements themselves, what you
would call the hard minerals, what you
would call rocks, what you would call
boulders, what you would call foothills,
what you would call mountains, there is
another system that is concurrent with
what we are describing that uses the
energy web in a different way.
One thing that only very few of your
scientists have begun to realize and are
beginning to investigate
is that there is what we might term a
deep resonance field that exists that is
generally speaking on a vibratory level
that is below your ability to sense. If
you are sensitive enough, you can feel
it. You can tap into it. But generally
speaking, it is not always audible to
you. It is a very deep thrumming
vibrating resonant energy. the deep
energy resonance field that is part of
the electromagnetic field of your planet
that it issues. But it is tuned and
pitched in such a way that it actually
forms a communication network between
all of the crystallin minerals and rocks
and mountains on your planet. This is
the vibratory level of the nature of
that kind of consciousness of mineral or
crystallin consciousness and it
communicates readily in a variety of
ways through that deep resonance field.
Now some of your scientists are also
beginning to understand and realize that
everything is made of consciousness.
Everything is self-aware in its own way.
It may not be self-aware in the way that
you express it, but nevertheless, it is
still a reflection. It knows itself as a
reflection of all that is in its own
way, in its own interpretation. And they
are recognizing that consciousness is
pervasive and permeates everything in
creation. Very few cuttingedge quantum
physicists are beginning to explore
this. The term they have used for this
is called pans psychism
or the idea that they are now beginning
to express that there is a
protoconciousness
field that exists everywhere and out of
which consciousness in its various forms
of expression may arise.
So the protoconsciousness
field itself is another way that many
beings throughout creation will form
this sort of energy net and energy web.
This is generally what is used by what
you would call animals on your planet,
humans on your planet in a variety of
ways. They tap into the idea of this
consciousness field
and based on the configuration of the
consciousness, in other words, what kind
of a being it is because the kind of
being you are is a description of how
you are energetically arranged as a kind
of a matrix to filter this consciousness
field through yourself and express it in
the ways that are gerine and relevant
for the description of what you are of
who you are. So animals, humans, all
that kind of life will utilize the
consciousness field and will through
themselves filter it in such a way as to
create different frequencies, different
vibrations that are given off that are
specific to those particular types of
animals, those particular types of
beings. So this is what it means when
you learn to talk cat, talk dog, talk
fox, talk dolphin, talk any kind of
animal is picking up on the specific
resonant frequency of the consciousness
field that they are using their
particular wavelength, their particular
well if you wish radio station
to dial in yourself to those
frequencies. Now the idea of humanity in
a sense not being in any way, shape or
form better than any of this has itself
by definition one interesting and
unusual difference in all of this. And
that is not that other animals can't do
it if they need to, but the idea of
humanity of what you would call
sensiency in your form has the ability
to actually and is built into the
ability to actually go up and down the
range of these frequencies we are
describing so that you can tune in. So
that you can in a sense funnel through
you all the different wavelengths, all
the different frequencies, all the
different forms of communication and
resonance to express an amalgamation of
these ideas, a kind of combination, a
kind of synergy of all these ideas. You
are the form on earth that can process
all of this into one large overall
understanding and expression of hololism
on your planet. Which is why you think
of yourselves in many ways as the
stewards of the earth of the land, the
humans of the sea, the dolphins and the
whales. So the dolphins and whales also
have this ability to go through a range
of frequencies very naturally to pick up
on and tie together and link together
and express synergistically the idea of
many different kinds of forms of life
and expressions on your planet. This is
why in a sense it is given to you to be
the caretakers. Now in the past because
of negative definitions and negative
belief systems many humans on your
planet have thought that this meant that
you have domination over all the other
life on your planet. This is not the
case. In the old interpretation
in some of your ancient scriptures where
it says that mankind has dominion over
the earth and all life on earth. The
ancient term dominion in that sense
meant caretaker not overlord. So the
idea is dominion is given to you to be
the one to process and synergize and
caretake and represent all the different
forms of life on your planet and nurture
and support and give life to all of
these things along with them in a way
that creates this holistic net to be
amplified and magnified so that all life
forms can pick up on the information
they require. to sustain themselves in
the best possible way, the most
beneficial possible way for all concern.
In a sense, you have the ability to
actually become the frequency of the net
itself and thus in any given situation
or circumstance connect into whatever
kind of consciousness expression you
need to. Be it the trees, be it the
animals, be it the rocks. By simply
being sensitive enough to the fact that
you are the synergizers to go within
yourself and get more precise ability to
tell the difference between the
different frequencies that are expressed
by the different forms of life. So that
in honing in on those frequencies, you
can have the kinds of ongoing
communication and exchange of
information that is possible to have
with all the different forms of life on
your planet. You form your own nature
social network on a certain resonant
frequency that is itself representative
of the combination of all the
frequencies. Is this making some sense
to you?
>> Yes.
>> All right. So the idea again is that of
course everything expresses itself in a
different way, a different modality
and it's about really tuning in and in a
sense taking on the mantle of that
modality and expressing it as strongly
through your reflective aspects, your
reflective nature as you possibly can to
strengthen and amplify and reinforce
that modality for that form of life. So
when you are learning to communicate
with a dog, with a cat, with a bird, you
are actually taking on the resonance,
fine-tuning to that resonance and
reflecting it back in a way that
actually starts a back and forth kind of
energy beat. And in that energy beat, as
it levels itself into that particular
frequency, you then start to perceive
communication in the form in which it is
expressed from that animal. because you
are expressing that aspect within
yourself because you contain all those
frequencies that are representative of
all the animals and all the trees and
all the rocks and the sky and the sea
and everything on your planet. So, it's
about becoming a very fine-tuned
station, a very fine-tuned antenna,
receiver, and transmitter so that you
can really start to perceive those
different frequencies in a very fine
grained way and really lock into them
much more strongly so that you can
amplify that vibration between yourself
and the life form you are communicating
with. And then start to really interpret
and transceive the communication in the
modality that it is expressing itself
from. because you become like them. This
is the secret of the shamans in the
sense of actually being able to tap into
parallel realities in such a way that
they actually represent themselves as
the animal they are in communication
with. This is the source of the idea of
seeing shamans turn into birds turn into
jaguars turn into various animals. It's
not in a sense that any molecular
rearrangement has happened. What is
happening is that like the sages that
Willa has spoken of, they have the
ability to understand their connection
to parallel versions of themselves in
parallel realities so strongly that they
can actually represent themselves and
bring in a representation from a
parallel reality strongly enough that
you actually perceive that parallel
reality representation instead of the
human form that was basically in the
parallel reality that you inhabit. So
they are presenting a reflective mirror
so strongly that you think they have
actually changed their shape. You follow
me?
>> But all you're getting is a reflection
from a parallel reality because the
shaman is being a perfect mirror angled
at just the correct angle to reflect
that parallel reality expression of
their consciousness from another
parallel reality into your
consciousness. So a shaman is a perfect
mirror that operates at different angles
reflecting different realities to you.
You understand?
It is not about the idea of molecular
change. That's not what shape shifters
do. They take advantage of this
consciousness field in such a way as to
extend beyond the consciousness field of
what you consider to be your universe
and go into the consciousness field of
other universes and therefore can
reflect things and expressions of
consciousness from those other parallel
realities in to the reality in which
they originated.
So this all comes down to the idea that
you are enscconced in, embedded in,
immersed in a titanic infinite social
network of energy webs at certain
vibratory levels. And you can tap into
these more consciously as you start to
explore within yourself.
caretaker nature to all of nature and
remind yourself again first and foremost
that you are not above nature not below
nature not separate from nature but our
nature. So find your natural selves.
This is why we suggest to you in many
occasions that it's not about finding
out how to be normal. It's about finding
out how to be your natural self because
your natural self is tapped in does
understand these connections. And when
you relax the idea of what you think
you're supposed to be and actually allow
yourself to be what you are as nature
expressed you, you will find yourself
being a part of nature, not separate
from it. And these kinds of
communications and your ability to tap
into nature's social network you will
find will already be inherent within
your skills, your talents, your
abilities to perceive this more and more
readily. Does this make sense?
>> All right. So let us proceed in a
natural way and open up to the idea of
sharing at this time if you wish.
As you prepare
a little say we will continue the
transmission by suggesting and
encouraging each and every one of you to
relax.
Start breathing gently,
deeply, easily, effortlessly,
and let go of the cares of the day. You
are here and you are now, and there is
nowhere more important to be.
So allow yourselves to continue to
breathe gently,
easily,
deeply.
As your lights begin to play and your
music begins to play, allow yourselves
to fall into the dream [music]
and drift with us in your consciousness.
As you gaze upon the holotope
and realize that what you are looking at
is a reflection of your own
consciousness
and all the lines of light and
information and energy that stretch out
from you [music]
toward all probabilities.
And as you remember the experiment and
the exercise that we did this day
and those things that were duplicated,
reinforced and strengthened that may not
be to your preference. [music]
And those things that were duplicated,
reinforced, and strengthened
that were in alignment with who you
prefer to be.
Allow yourselves to see
in the different directions of the
spirals and the lines.
Those lines leading to all of those
probabilities,
negative and positive, positive and
negative with you at the center
in the Trinity spot of neutrality
where all things are equal and all
things are valid.
And even though there may be things that
are not in alignment with your
preference there, they are nevertheless
equally valid as choices and experiences
within all that is. [music]
So that you can learn by staying in that
neutral space.
to choose what you prefer
without invalidating what you do not
prefer and giving it more energy than it
requires. Just to be. Just to be.
[music]
Just to be.
For just because you can see it doesn't
mean it will affect you. [music]
But now that you are aware of where the
collective consciousness focus might be,
you can begin to stretch your
imagination along those lines of light
and begin to allow information to come
to you from parallel realities that
exist simultaneously with your
experience,
but which are more reflective and
representative
of The reality experiences you prefer
that are representative of your joy, of
your passion,
of your truth,
your being, your essence, your core,
[music] your signature frequency
of life, light, and love.
And remember [music]
that this transmission
was titled the window of opportunity and
discovery. [music]
This discovery is an opportunity for
you. with this new title. To realize
that you always, no matter what you
discover within yourselves, individually
or collectively, that that discovery is
always an opportunity
for change, for expansion, for growth,
[music] for experience that serves and
supports and nurtures life,
love and light.
And nothing [music]
is chiseled in steel or stone
that does not represent [music] your
best essential selves. For you are the
ones to chart the course of your life.
Regardless of what anyone else may
choose,
allow yourself to feel [music] the
currents that draw you toward the shores
that you prefer to inhabit.
toward the shores that you prefer to
discover
within the infinite sea of your being.
[music]
You create the maps.
You chart the course. You are the
compass needle pointing to your magnetic
north, your truth,
[music] your essence,
your journey along with all the other
journeys that harmonize in their own way
with yours. [music]
Different paths all leading to the same
effect [music]
of passion and joy, creativity and love
and the expressions of them in your life
because that is the essence of your
being. The true power
that requires the gentlest touch.
No force required, no force necessary
for the current flows already to those
places that you need to go. All you need
to do is find the appropriate current
that is you and let it take you. Let it
guide you. [music]
Let it pull you towards more of
yourself, towards discovering more of
who you are.
Allow yourself to drift and dream within
that current and know that every change
within you is a total and complete
change of the entirety of the universe
you experience.
You never step into the same river
twice. [music]
There are more branches on the tree than
you can see. And there is always a new
alternative and a new path
that is more harmonious and in alignment
with the true essential being that you
are.
A more natural path
that allows you to know that you are not
just in nature but you are nature.
an expression of the creativity [music]
of existence itself. An extension and a
reflection of all that is that you are
discovering more and more of every day
in every way with your intentions
[music] to be at peace
in love
in light
and express yourself as harmonious life.
harmonious life.
[music] For that is the true definition
of life is to be in harmony and to
expand
and to integrate [music]
and to know yourself.
Chart those courses
on that map on the endless sea of
discovery. That is the essence of your
being. That is the essence
of creation. [music]
And as you stand on the deck of that
ship,
[music] the wind in your sails
and the salt air in your lungs. [music]
Take a deep breath in and feel alive
and let it out. and add that breath to
the sails so they may billow and carry
you forth ever more swiftly upon that
sea.
And take another deep breath in
and feel invigorated and refreshed and
alive.
And exhale into the sail that it may
carry you forth ever more swiftly upon
that sea.
And take a deep breath in and feel
the vibrations of your being. And hold
it and hold it
and blow it into the sail.
For now you are
the winds of change.
The winds that guide you, [music] that
fill your sails,
propelling you along that current,
leading you to those beautiful shores,
[music]
those brilliant shores, the sunlit
shores, the moonlit shores upon which
beautiful wave after wave after wave
of life and light and intellig igence
and brilliance and consciousness and
beauty and grace
wash upon those shore
and you land upon that shore.
[music]
And though it may be to you
an uncharted land, it is still a land
made of you. And every new footstep and
footprint you leave upon that beach is
made within your consciousness and
awakens within you more memory, more
understanding, and more realization of
the shores upon which you now walk. and
opens up before you a magnificent and
amazing vista of life. Trees and lush
jungles that contain mysteries and
secrets of beauty
and priceless
gems of discovery
of consciousness of awareness of
reflectivity
of self-awareness
within you. Treasure chest upon treasure
chest lies on these shores for you to
discover.
>> [music]
>> to appreciate
yourselves and grow in value within
yourselves within your own understanding
and relationship to yourselves.
the deepest appreciation like the
deepest parts of the ocean.
And the lofty gratitude and grace of the
infinite blue skies and the space and
stars above and the land and the sea
that stretches out before you. [music]
You stand upon the shores of discovery
before an infinite horizon
never ends. [music]
Chart your course.
[music]
Pay attention to where you are.
Pay attention
to what you hear.
Pay attention to what you know to be
true. [music]
and chart your course
and arrive upon those shores
and discover
not only more of yourself but all the
reflections that are waiting there for
you.
The reflections
of us, the reflections [music]
of your guides, the reflections of your
higher mind, the reflections of your
ancestors, the reflections of your
descendants, the reflections of all of
the simultaneous concurrent parallel
nows
[music]
Connect
to what you need for it is given to you
easily and effortlessly and joyfully.
Accept the gifts that creation has to
give. Accept the gifts of creation that
you are. Give the gifts that you are to
those waiting for them so that they may
also
chart a course and discover [music]
the shores of their being in the
uncharted waters that lay before you.
[music]
Allow yourself to drift and dream
upon the currents of the infinite sea.
Swim in the depths and drink deeply of
life [music]
and be refreshed
and feel alive.
[music]
And ponder
and ponder
and ponder the probabilities
that lay before you. [music]
that lay within you,
the probability engine that you are.
[music]
Choose.
Choose. [music]
Allow yourself to take a deep breath in
and let it out.
>> [music]
>> Allow yourself to take a deep breath in
and let it out.
Allow yourself to take a deep breath in
and hold it and hold it and hold it
and let go
of everything that is no longer relevant
for who you prefer to be. [music]
Be at ease.
Be at peace. [music] Be in joy.
Be you.
Allow your music to soften.
Allow your lights to dim [music]
and continue to just breathe gently and
easily and float freely in the void
that contains all probabilities. For it
is not empty, though it may sometimes
seem to be so. But in the silence
you will find your voice.
Continue now to just drift and dream
gently with us for a time. [music]
Remember,
when you are surrounded
By darkness, it is easier to see the
light within.
Welcome home.